# Ariel Karas

**DevOps Engineer** 

## Contact

**Address** 

Givatayim

Phone

+972 58-470-0739

E-mail

Ariel1434@gmail.com

## Skills

IT solution development

Maintenance and troubleshooting

**Technical Writing** 

Testing and maintenance

CI/CD

Linux

Docker

**Python** 

# Languages

Hebrew-Native

English-Upper intermediate

DevOps Engineer with more than 8 years of experience in Electronic and Computer Engineering. Skilled in AWS, Kubernetes, and CI/CD management. Dedicated to automation via Terraform and Ansible.

Distinct graduate from iNT-college at the open university, emphasizing continuous learning, collaboration, and efficiency.

# **Work History**

# 2022 - 2023 DevOps Intern and IT Helpdesk Technician

Tactivision Service Ltd, Tel-Aviv

- Interned while completing SRE DevOps Engineering course.
- Managed IT support, networking, and systems.
- Automated routine documentation processes.

#### 2020 - 2021 Network Technician

Inbar Solar Energy Ltd, Airport City

- Tested network communication for PV Plant electrical cabinets.
- Led communication teams onsite.
- Collaborated with international engineering teams on communication cabinets.

# **Accomplishments**

## **Network Technician, Inbar Solar Company (2021)**

 Diagnosed recurring network issues and introduced a customer-accessible router restart button. This initiative notably reduced field calls, improving operational efficiency and customer satisfaction.

## **Military Service Accomplishment** (2018)

 Revived old robotic systems without having their original guides. Created simple user manuals which are still used for robot maintenance.

# **Education**

2022 - 2023 S.R.E DevOps Engineer: Information Technology

INT College-institute of Innovation & Technology - Tel-Aviv

2013 - 2015 Practical Engineer in Computers & Electronics: Electrical Engineering

ORT College - Rehovot